The best in the business is back in the game.
Transporter 2 is a action, thriller, crime film directed by Louis Leterrier.
Professional driver, and former Special Forces officer, Frank Martin is living in Miami, where he is temporarily
filling in for a friend as the chauffeur for a government narcotics control policy director and his family.
The young boy in the family is targeted for kidnapping, and Frank immediately
becomes involved in protecting the child and exposing the kidnappers.
Frank Martin, played by Jason Statham.
Audrey Billings, played by Amber Valletta.
Gianni Chellini, played by Alessandro Gassmann.
Lola, played by Kate Nauta.
Jefferson Billings, played by Matthew Modine.
Dimitri, played by Jason Flemyng.
Transporter 2 (French: Le Transporteur 2) is a 2005 English-language French action film
directed by Louis Leterrier and written by Luc Besson & Robert Mark Kamen.
It is the sequel to The Transporter (2002) and the second installment in the Transporter franchise,
followed by Transporter 3 (2008) and The Transporter Refueled, also called Transporter 4.
It stars Jason Statham as Frank Martin, with Alessandro Gassmann, Amber Valletta,
Kate Nauta, François Berléand, Matthew Modine, and Jason Flemyng.
In the film, Frank Martin (Statham) is tasked with protecting the young son of
politician Jefferson Billings (Modine) from an international drugs cartel.
Transporter 2 was theatrically released in France on August 3, 2005, by EuropaCorp, and was
released in the United States on September 2, 2005, by 20th Century Fox.
It received mixed reviews from critics with praise for Statham's performance,
action sequences and direction, but criticism for its screenwriting.
It grossed $89.1 million worldwide and was followed
by the sequel Transporter 3 (2008).
The film explores themes of martial arts, chauffeur,
miami, florida, workaholic, war on drugs.
The tone is intense.